To be continued...
The participants are seriously Year
bonsai
Welcome
Did you go inside?
Yes, I practiced hard yesterday
And而且
They have been in the best of their
ability as trainees
from the first day to the next round
and what is in practice today?
Special lesson for 2 groups of trainees
The first one is
I'm Kusanagi Miyashita. Nice to meet
you.
Nice to meet you.
The popular comedian, Kusanagi
Miyashita, will challenge himself to a
variety show.
When you're doing idol activities, you
can't avoid variety shows.
I think it will be a good experience.
The members who are chosen by the MVP
will get a barbecue at the end of the
day.
I'm excited.
The first round is a huge balloon
explosion game.
It's a very popular game. You have to
pass the giant balloon and answer the
question.
The person who explodes at the right
time loses.
It's a game where you can react quickly.
I'll have 10 people and Kusanagi do it.
Do you have any advice for the giant
balloon?
I've never done a giant balloon.
Why?
The first challenge begins.
The first question is, what kind of
comedian do you think is interesting?
Ready, start!
Ariyoshi.
What are you saying?
I don't know what you're saying.
Garu Garu.
Ayana.
Tsukimura.
Ayama.
What are you saying?
Panic.
What is this sound?
Stop!
What is this?
I can't hear anything.
Everyone is just giving it away.
Ready, start!
Attack!
Wait a minute.
I went to the Chikuwabu twice.
Why did you go to the Chikuwabu twice?
I will start.
U에
Three out.
OK.
One, two, three!
Noooooooo!
Nooooooo!
Thank you for watching!
I've never wished to break it like this
What is the next variety show?
What is in the box?
It's a variety show!
Next, she challenges a very, very
standard technique.
At last year's training camp, she showed
a wonderful demonstration.
On behalf of the team, I would like to
introduce Kashiwagi-san.
There is, there is, there is.
There is.
She is so strong.
Did you understand it in the box?
What?
Re sample
The iron
I'm in trouble!
What?
It's moving.
Is there something?
The most interesting thing...
This is the contents
Ahhhh
Oh man
Thank you for watching.
No way.
I'm really going to bite it.
This is the worst.
This is bad.
This is very painful.
This is the type.
Be careful.
This is painful.
This is terrible.
Can you answer?
Please answer.
Squid.
You're kidding.
It's not squid.
The MVP is Karen.
Congratulations.
I wonder what's inside the box.
The reaction was interesting and the
answer was squid.
It was interesting, so please rate it.
Congratulations Karen.
Congratulations.
Next special training.
The director of the movie, The Camera,
Japan, won the 8th Academy Awards.
It's Shinichiro Ueda.
Thank you.
Shinichiro Ueda, who was the director of
the movie, The Camera, Japan, won the
award.
In addition,
I'm not a
He has been active in many ways,
including in dramas and stages.
Acting is also a point for members to
act.
So, I will challenge the acting lesson
by Director Ueda.
I will start acting using the script.
The lesson starts with the script
prepared by the director.
The script is divided into one page,
which has very few lines and the second
half is played in ad-lib.
At first, I was like this.
Try to do it as you feel, without
putting too much effort into your
shoulders
Yes
First, Yuna and Nonoka will try
Kaori and Misato
Ready, start!
It's a scene where they find a classmate
with the same hobby
They are trying to find a classmate with
the same hobby
Um...
Yes?
Do you like it?
What?
No, I just borrowed it from a friend.
I see. I thought you didn't read it
around you, so you liked it.
No, I just really like it.
Really?
You lived next door, right?
Yes, I did.
I didn't know you liked it.
You don't have it often, do you?
What are you reading here?
I still like it.
Thank you.
How about you, Yuna?
I thought I had a little bit of a
shyness.
I didn't have a friend like that in my
generation.
But it was a little difficult to express
my feelings of being shy.
I see.
Yuna struggled to express her feelings
with acting.
Next, Ruri and Yuka will try.
Ready...
Yes!
I'm sorry, too late
I will play again
Bye
See you
Thank you for watching.
Do you like me?
I'm sorry.
I don't read much, so I thought you
liked me.
Do you like me?
Maybe I like you.
I might have seen you for the first
time.
I read all of them.
I don't know.
Which group did you choose?
Me?
Which group?
I'm close.
Let's read them together.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
What are you reading?
I'm reading the fan letters.
It was fun.
I read it too.
Thank you.
How was it?
When I do this,
I can express my feelings in my heart.
It's difficult to express it in my
heart.
Acting is difficult.
Where is the classroom?
The classroom is next to me.
I'll go there and show you.
I'm sorry.
They don't know how to express their
feelings.
They are struggling.
Then...
There are two parts in this script
that I don't usually write like this.
In fact, this script has a trick.
The part where Kaori is worried about
his homework.
And the part where he suppresses his
excitement.
This is emotion.
The script is a principle to write what
is reflected in the camera.
For example, if you want to write in a
state where you are worried about your
feelings,
you should write that you are holding
your head towards your homework
or that you are breathing deeply.
In the script, not only emotions are
written like this,
but also specific movements are often
written.
However, the director deliberately gave
the script with the cut movement.
Why is that?
The director wanted to show that acting
is acting.
I want you to remember
Acting is acting
In fact, when expressing the emotions in
the mind with acting
It is an important point to express the
feelings by replacing them with
movements
I was cutting the movement part to
notice it
I think I was doing something like a
thought-provoking style
I want you to replace it with a specific
action
Like holding your head
Or standing up and breathing deeply
Or massaging your neck
One more important point of acting was
told by the director
The reason why Misato called her that
way
What was the reason for this?
I was walking and thinking about it
I wanted to hear it
When I could express Misato's feelings,
I looked back
In this case, it is better to make a
trigger in the other person
You can act without acting
Misato wants to talk to you, but you are
doing homework
So it's hard to talk to you
So, you want to talk to her when she is
feeling down
In school, when you want to talk to her
It's hard to talk to her when she is
talking with her friends
But you want to talk to her when she is
feeling down
I think your actions are different
depending on the other person
So, you want to make a trigger in the
other person
To make a trigger in the other person's
action
This is the point to act naturally
Like everyday life
After looking at the other person's
action
The students were told the importance of
acting against it
The director taught them two points and
they tried to act the same way again
What will the students' acting change?
The students were told the importance of
acting against it
1, 2, 3, 4
I'm sorry?
Um...
Yes?
Do you like me?
What?
I like you, but maybe...
Aren't there many people who read your
letter?
I was surprised.
I didn't think you'd say that.
I'm glad.
You read it before.
That's great.
Thank you.
How was it? Compared to the first time?
Compared to the first time,
I was able to answer the most difficult
questions.
You had a good timing to talk to me.
I was able to talk to you.
But I couldn't say it yet.
I didn't think it was the same as usual.
It's almost useful.
I was wondering if I could talk to you.
Thank you.
These two are also...
Ready, start!
Do you like it?
What?
Did you read it?
I was reading the book.
I like reading books.
I like this too.
I see.
I'm glad that no one reads the book.
I'm sorry.
I was so close to the end.
Thank you.
It was very natural.
When I passed by here, I glanced at it.
Was it natural?
Or did you decide to go here?
It was natural.
I felt that the sound was a little
lower.
Until then, I was focused on that.
It was very natural.
It was wonderful. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thus, all of them continued to act while
receiving the guidance of Director Ueda.
It's interesting.
I really like it.
When the acting with reality was born.
Thank you very much.
Lesson is over.
I think that there was a way to use it
not only for acting but also for singing
and dancing.
I'm looking forward to meeting the
director and actress at the scene of a
movie or drama someday.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
I don't think I've ever received any
advice from Director Ueda.
I think it was a really good experience.
I didn't have any acting experience.
I got a lot of advice and I couldn't do
it.
I did it, but I still have regrets. I
wanted to do it a little more.
Ten students who have had an
irreplaceable experience of receiving
direct guidance from one of the movie
directors representing Japan.
And then...
To become a member in the debut, they
will go to the lesson again
The final evaluation is approaching
If I can learn choreography
I will be the only one who is failing
The training camp is in full swing
The MBC's meat is being served
Congratulations, Haru-chan
Amazing
It's very hot
I'll eat
The MBC's meat is being served
Thank you very much
Bye bye, see you next time